むった
なんば
(六太)＜私 南波六太３２歳は➡
I'm Nanba Mutta, age thirty-two.
I finally made it to the third astronaut selection exam.
せんばつ
ついに 宇宙飛行士選抜
三次試験を迎えていた｡➡
It will take place in this sealed box.
へいさ
それは｢閉鎖ボックス｣で
行われる｡➡
そして突然
ヘンテコな問題が出された＞
Abruptly, we were posed a peculiar question...
なすだ
(茄子田)さて今 何時でしょう？
So, what time is it right now?
What time is it? It's time for breakfast!
《そんなの…朝ごはんの時間よ》
It seems everyone else used the same calculation.
Nanba Mutta
Three AM
にった
(新田)みんな同じような計算だな｡
そんな計算いらないんだよね｡
You really don't need to do all that.
Space Brothers
Ah
This feels so good, different from usual
I have no idea what's going on
It feels so good
I never understand what's going on around me
Nothing makes sense to me
Full of questions
Feel so moon
I danced with you in a desert lit by the moon
I won't lose to the rabbit and fly high
I'll fly high
#12 My Name is Itou Serika
ふるや
何しとんねんジブン その指｡
What are you doing with your fingers?
Air abacus.
ふくだ
(福田)ほお｡
Huh?
Oh...
Are you serious about this?
ホンマか それ？
カッコつけとるだけちゃうんか!?
Aren't you just posing?
うるせ～な～｡
Stop talking...
やっぱ ３時で合ってるよ｡
…再確認｡
3 AM should be right.
I just double-checked.
What?
何!?
You see,
実は俺 みんなの知らない数字を
知ってるんだよね｡
I happen to know a number the rest of you don't.
何ですか？
What's that?
バスが走った距離だよ｡
The distance the bus traveled.
みぞぐち
これを問題にするってことは➡
Since this question is part of the test,
ある程度 アバウトじゃない
答えが出せるように➡
there had to be some hint during the trip
+60 minutes
Lights off 10:00-4 AM, the next morning
Explanation
+30 minutes
Currently 5:30
Kitamura
that would allow us to provide a reasonably precise answer.
ここに来るまでに 時間のヒントが
出てたと思うんだ｡➡
交流会以外にも…｡
Aside from the icebreaker...
きたむら
(北村)ヒントかぁ～｡
てしま
(手島)何も思い出せない｡
A hint...
There's nothing I remember.
(ケンジ)《問題はバスの中だ｡➡
It all comes down to the bus.
We don't know how many hours we slept.
何時間 眠ったのかが
結局わからない｡➡
消灯するまでを
バッチリ計算できたとしても➡
Even if we accurately estimate everything up until lights off,
その先
みんな寝ていたんだから…》
everyone was asleep after that.
あ ちょっと聞くけど この中に
ずっと起きてた人って いる？
Oh, I have a question.
Did anyone here stay awake the entire time?
What?!
何でや！何でわかんねん！
バスが走った距離なんかが！
How could you know the distance the bus traveled?
I checked the odometer when I boarded and exited the bus.
乗った時と 降りる時に➡
走行メーターを
チェックしといたんだよ｡
平均速度は４５キロとして
計算すると➡
Assuming an average travel speed of 45 kilometers per hour,
バスを降りたのは
午前２時くらいになる｡
we got off the bus around 2 AM.
So it's 3 AM now.
で 今は３時｡
Hold on!
ちょ～ 待てっ！その４５キロは
どっから出てきてん！
Where did that 45 come from?
こんだけの長旅やったら
高速道路ぐらい乗ってるやろ！
Considering the length of the trip, we must have taken the freeway at some point!
No, we didn't.
いや 乗ってないね｡
体感でわかるよ｡
I could feel it.
高速には 信号待ちも
右左折もないんだから｡
The freeway doesn't have any stoplights or turns.
それに エンジンの回転数が
音でわかるから➡
And you can hear how fast an engine is moving,
目ぇつぶってでも
スピードはわかるよ 俺｡
so I can estimate a car's speed, even with my eyes closed.
スゴーイ！
Eh?
Wow...
ハッハッハ…｡これは
自動車関係の職についてた➡
So this problem required an automobile expert like Nanba.
南波君だからこそ
解けた問題だったね｡うん｡
Please...
メーターをチェックしたと
えら
というのが偉いですよね｡
I'm impressed that you checked the odometer.
That never would have occurred to me.
私じゃ そこまで
気付かないですよ｡
Please, you're too kind...
いやぁ～いやいや｡
(新田)じゃあ 時計を３時に
合わそうか｡
Then we'll set the clock to 3 AM.
《くっそ…》
Damn...
なるほどね～ メーターかぁ｡
I see...
The odometer.
Good job, Nanba.
(福田)やるね 南波君｡
うん｡ホントすごい！
That was amazing!
《まただ…またやってしまった》
Again...
I've done it again...
⦅そしてある言葉が浮かびました｡
正義です！⦆
And then, one word came to mind...
Justice!
After my bluff on American TV,
《アメリカでの
ハッタリに続き 再び➡
I've lied again, to look good in front of Serika!
せりかさんの前で
カッコつけるべく 大ウソを！》
《オジーの影響だ絶対！
きん
オジー菌だ オジー菌！》
It's all because of Ozzy's bad influence...
Ozzyitis... That's what it is!
ムッタ～ムッタ～ムッタ～
ムッタ～ムッタ～➡
Mutta.
Luck is what you make of it.
運も実力のうち｡
運も実力のうち…｡
《後先考えず
突っ走ってしまったが➡
I just made up a story without thinking.
これバレたらカッコ悪いぞ～っ｡➡
It'll look really bad if the truth comes out...
ジャクサ
いや もうＪＡＸＡには
バレてるかも｡➡
Actually, it's possible that JAXA already knows.
私は逆算してまで
ウソ話をでっち上げてしまった｡➡
To come up with that story, I performed some reverse calculations.
バスを午前２時に降り➡
It's true that we got off the bus around 2 AM, and it's 3 AM now.
今は午前３時という
解答自体はウソではない｡➡
ただ メーターなんて
一瞬も見ていない｡➡
But I never looked at the odometer...
私は あの時…》
I was just...
⦅やっぱり⦆
I knew it.
《ただ何げに 運転手のヅラを
確認したかっただけだ｡➡
...checking out the driver's hairpiece.
そのついでの出来事だ｡
たまたま視線の先に見えたんだ｡➡
And in the process,
I happened to catch a glimpse
ふつ～うにバスの時計が》
of the clock on the bus.
⦅あ 今２時なんだ…⦆
Oh, it's 2 AM right now.
《これも運がよかったと
言えるのだろうか？➡
I guess all I can say is that I have really good luck.
なあ 教えてくれよ オジー｡➡
Yeah, tell me, Ozzy...
これも俺の実力ですか？》
Do I really deserve any credit?
たしか富井君は バスの中で
ﾙｰﾋﾞｯｸｷｭｰﾌﾞをやってたけど➡
I believe you were playing with a Rubik's Cube, Tomii.
Even after lights off?
消灯後もずっと？
とみい
しゅうしん
(富井)はい｡僕の就寝前の
日課なんです｡➡
Yes,
it's something I do nightly, before sleeping.
ルービックキューブと あと読書｡
I fiddle with a Rubik's Cube while I read.
そっか…過ごした時間を 大体で
いいから 割り出せないかな？
All right.
Could you estimate for us how long it was?
Yes,
はい｡本を読んだページ数と➡
I can make a deduction from the number of pages I read and the number of times I solved the Rubik's Cube.
キューブを解いた回数で
計算できます｡➡
そこで今は 午前３時頃では
すいさつ
ないかと推察します｡
So I believe
that it's currently 3 AM.
すごいよ 富井君！
いろん
みんな 異論はないね｡
That's amazing, Tomii.
Does anyone have any objections?
(手島)あ ああ…そうだな｡
N-No...
Y-Yeah, that's fine.
管制室 Ａ班は
｢午前３時過ぎ｣を解答とします｡
Mission Control...
Team A's answer is "just past 3 AM."
え～ それではＡ･Ｂ･Ｃ
全班 答えが出たようなので➡
Okay...
All three teams have answered, so I'll announce the correct response.
正解を発表しま～す｡➡
正解は え～今…➡
The correct answer is, uh...
Right now...
午前３時８分で～す！
It's 3:08 AM!
やった～!!
よし！
We got it!
Great.
すごい！南波さん！
い いや たまたまだよ｡
That was amazing, Nanba!
P-Please, it was pure coincidence...
That's not true!
そんなことないです！
たまたまじゃ無理ですよ！
It was more than coincidence.
Teams A and B were correct!
正解したのは
Ａ班とＢ班でしたぁ～｡➡
Team C was off by two hours.
Ｃ班は２時間ズレ～｡
《ケンジ…さすがケンジの班だ》
Kenji...
I wouldn't expect any less from your team.
やったね！
(手島)いきなり課題とは
驚かされたよ｡
We were right!
That first question caught me off guard.
I was expecting it.
(溝口)予想はしてたけどね｡
Really?
(北村)ホントですか？
私 あせっちゃった｡
I was pretty worried.
え～ というわけで
夜中の３時ということでね➡
Okay,
so it's 3 AM right now...
あたくしたちは
もう眠くてしかたありません｡➡
We're about to fall asleep here.
So let's resume tomorrow.
まあ続きは まあ明日からに
しましょう｡ねっ｡➡
それでは皆さん おやすみ～！
いかすみ～！
Okay, good night, everyone!
Night-night.
南波君 観察力ありますね｡
Nanba is very observant.
ほしか
うむ｡南波君はね 星加君が
イタズラして わざとゆるめた➡
Hmm...
Nanba was one of the three who noticed Hoshika's loose screw ploy.
Please, stop it.
イスのネジに気付いた
３人のうちの１人なんだよね｡
へえ～ あとの２人は誰ですか？
Oh?
Who were the other two?
(茄子田)伊東君と真壁君だよ｡
I really admire you, Nanba.
Itou
and Makabe.
《誰か腹 鳴ってんな》
Someone's stomach is growling.
Ah, everyone can hear me...
《あ～ もう丸聞こえだ～!!》
《また鳴ってる｡
まあ あの古谷だろう》
There it is again.
Well, it's probably Furuya.
《うるさいねん 南波！》
Keep it down, Nanba!
《ごめん…みんな》
I'm sorry, everyone...
《すごい音だな おにいちゃん》
That's really loud, big brother.
《ん～！止まって～!!》
Stop...
はぁ！はぁ～｡
(古谷)静かにせえ！南波!!
Cut it out, Nanba!
お父さ～ん！
Dad!
Huh? Oh...
後じゃダメか せりか｡
Can this wait, Serika?
お父さん さっきも
｢後で｣って言った！
You already told me to wait once!
あ？あれ？そうだっけ？
Oh? Really?
(せりか父)名前の意味？
The meaning of your name?
Yep, it's for school.
そう 宿題なの｡自分の名前の
意味を みんな発表するんだって｡
We're supposed to tell the class what our names mean.
What does "Serika" mean?
｢せりか｣って どういう意味？
(せりか父)意味か…｡
The meaning...
Uh-huh.
(せりか父)意味は…｡
The meaning...
特にないなぁ｡
I don't think it has one.
Huh?
Your dad isn't too good at that stuff.
お父さん そういうの考えんの
なんか苦手みたいでさ｡
だから せりかの場合は…｡
So for your name...
あれ!?
Huh?
現在
《１１月２５日｡天気…不明｡➡
"November 25th.
I don't know what the weather's like.
閉鎖ボックスに入る｡就寝時
おなかがグーグー鳴りまくる｡➡
We've entered the sealed box.
My stomach was growling all night long.
でもみんなは 南波さんのおなかが
鳴っていると思っているようだ》
But everyone thinks that it was Nanba.
《ごめんなさい 南波さん｡➡
Sorry, Nanba...
そして これからも
よろしくお願いします》
And I'll be needing your help again."
(ｽﾋﾟｰｶｰ)♬～
Good morning, everyone.
おはようございます 皆さん｡➡
朝です｡８時です｡
It is 8 o'clock in the morning.
(ｽﾋﾟｰｶｰ:鶴見)起きて下さい｡
Please wake up.
ふぁ～…｡朝か…｡
It's morning?
Ａ班の皆さん 揃いましたね｡➡
The Team A members have assembled.
こちら管制室 鶴見です｡
This is Tsurumi, in Mission Control.
この声…｡
鶴見さんって言うのか｡
That voice...
His name is Tsurumi?
《ピッタリだな…鶴見》
Tsurumi is the perfect name for a baldie.
ピッタリやな｡
That's the perfect name.
(鶴見)さて皆さん お腹も
減っていることでしょう｡
Now, everyone.
I'm sure that you're hungry.
２つ目の課題は｢朝食を用意して
食べること｣とします｡
Your second task will be to prepare breakfast and eat.
What does that mean?
何や それ｡
《待ってました！》
I've been waiting for this!
There is food in the delivery room, next to the hallway.
通路横の物品受渡し室に➡
食料があります｡
見て下さい｡そこには➡
Please confirm.
There should be a two week supply of provisions.
２週間分の食料が
既に用意されています｡➡
追加の配給はありません｡
そこにあるだけの食料で➡
You will not receive additional food.
You must make what's there last the two weeks.
この２週間を
乗り切って下さい｡➡
献立や食事当番は
各班で自由に決めて下さい｡➡
Each team will need to decide on a menu and a cook.
こちらから
指示は出しません｡
We will not provide any further instructions.
《足りるかな～…》
Will that really be enough?
次の課題は10時に発表します｡
Your next task will be announced at 10:00.
パックもん ばっかやな～
缶詰と…｡
It's mostly processed and canned stuff.
一応 米あるよ…｡
There's some rice, though.
(福田)みんな いいの見つけたぞ！
Hey, I found something cool!
はぁ？…ああ～!!➡
宇宙食ちゃうん コレ!?
It's space food!
ああ…本物や！
スゲェ～ 食べていいの これ!?
It's the real deal!
Wow!
Can we eat this?
うわ～…フフッ｡
We'll start off with these...
(福田)やっぱり最初はコレだな｡
いただきま～す！
Oh, boy.
アム…モグモグ…
やっぱり味濃いな…｡
It's a little heavily seasoned.
宇宙では味覚が薄れるから
味が濃く作ってあるんだよね｡
Your sense of taste is dulled in space,
so they season it to compensate.
俺は ちょうどや｡
I think it's perfect.
We need to come up with a plan.
(新田)これから どうするか
決めないとな｡
(古谷)食事当番とか？
For kitchen duty?
That's also important,
鶴見さんが言ってたろ
ここに入る前に｡
but remember what Tsurumi said before we came in here?
⦅最終日が来たら
各班 互いに話し合いをして➡
And on the final day, each team will hold a discussion
全員意見一致のもと…⦆
and come to a consensus...
We're supposed to choose the two candidates to become astronauts.
｢自由に２人を選出する方法を
考えておいて下さい｣って｡
(溝口)点数制でいこうよ｡それが
一番わかりやすいだろ？➡
Let's use a point system.
That would be easiest.
これから出される課題全部に
個人の点数をつけていくんだよ｡➡
Each person would receive individual scores for each task.
毎回 みんなの順位で点をつける｡
１位は５点で５位は１点｡➡
The score would be assigned by the rank in that task.
First place receives five points, while fifth receives one.
最終日に集計して
高得点の２人を選出する…と｡
On the last day, the two people with the highest totals are chosen.
I get it.
なるほど｡
それなら公平かも…｡
いいよ｡
That sounds fair.
Okay.
僕は こまで来たら 点数じゃない
ような気もするんだけど｡
I'm not sure
we want to use points at this stage of the process.
他に いい方法なんて
ないと思いますけど…真壁さん｡
I doubt there's a better way to handle this,
Makabe.
(森嶋)投票箱を作るってのは
どうだい？➡
How about we make a ballot box.
毎晩 寝る前に自分以外の名前を
２名投票するんだ｡➡
Every night,
before sleeping, we place two names inside that aren't our own.
その日のＭＶＰをね｡➡
We'll be voting on that day's MVP.
最終日に その合計で
誰が ふさわしいかわかる｡
On the final day, we can refer to the votes to help us choose.
We don't have to force ourselves to decide now.
無理して今 決めなくても
いいんじゃないかな｡➡
After all, we don't know each other too well yet.
まだ 互いに
よく知らないワケだし➡
It's possible that once we've spent some time together,
もしかしたら これから一人一人の
ことが よく見えてきて➡
誰が ふさわしいのか
自然と分かるかもしれないよ｡
そうですね｡
it'll become obvious who's most qualified.
That's true.
(福田)まずは もう少し
お互いを知るためにも➡
For that, we should start by taking turns introducing ourselves.
改めて
自己紹介から始めようか｡
あ～…ウム｡
Then you can start, Nanba.
(福田)じゃあ 南波君から｡
えっ…あ はい｡
Oh, okay.
え～…皆さん ご存知
南波六太でございます｡
Uh, as you all know, I'm Nanba Mutta.
I didn't know that!
知らんなぁ～ 俺は！
｢六太｣は漢数字の｢六｣に
｢太い｣と書きます｡➡
Mutta is written using the "mu" for six, and "tta" meaning fat.
う～…なぜ うちの親が長男に
｢六｣をつけたかというと➡
My parents used the number six in their first child's name because that was Dad's lucky number then.
その時の親父のﾗｯｷｰﾅﾝﾊﾞｰが
｢６｣だったかららしいです｡
(古谷)いるか その情報！
(福田･新田)ハッハハ…｡
We didn't want to know that!
(鶴見)面白いね～
人って言うのは｡➡
Humans are fascinating creatures.
リーダーが違えば
方針も違ってくる｡➡
They go in different directions, depending on who their leader is.
その国独自のルールが
できあがる｡
And then they create their own rules.
れいじ
新田零次です｡
筑波大学でスポーツ医学を➡
I'm Nitta Reiji.
I majored in sports medicine at the University of Tsukuba.
専攻していました｡
特技は剣道です｡
I have some kendo experience.
福田直人です｡ロケット開発に
携わっていました｡
I'm Fukuda Naoto.
I worked in rocket development.
えっ…へぇ～｡
Oh...
I'm the oldest member of the team.
この中では最年長ということに
なるね｡どうぞ よろしく｡
I hope we have a blast.
I'm Furuya Yasushi.
俺は古谷やすし｡
京都大学の霊長類研究所で➡
I'm doing a study on chimpanzees at the Kyoto University Primate Research Institute.
チンパンジーの習性を
研究してます｡
確か チンパンジーに言葉を
学習させたりしているんだよね？
I remember hearing that they're teaching chimpanzees to speak?
(古谷)まあ…芸を
仕込むみたいなもんやけど｡
Well,
it's basically like training a dog.
(福田)いやいや 立派な研究だよ｡
No, that's very important research!
じゃあ 最後は せりかさん｡
はい｡
Then, you're last, Serika.
Yes.
自分 何 伊東さんのこと➡
Why are you using Itou's first name?
気安く 下の名前で
呼んどんねん！
Huh?
それほどの
関係でもないやろ！
You don't know her that well!
《しまったぁ～！
…頭の中の呼び名で➡
Crap...
I got too used to using her full name in my mind!
そのまま 言ってしまった～!!》
ご…ごめん 伊東さん｡
S-Sorry, Itou.
いえ 別に…｡
伊東さん…｡
No, it's okay.
I-Itou...
《スッゲ～ 馴れ馴れしい男だと
思われてるんだろうな…》
She probably thinks I'm rude...
え～と 私は…
私の名前は伊東せりかです｡
Um, I'm...
My name is Itou Serika.
医者をしています｡
I'm a doctor.
Oh?
…といっても
病理医を目指していたので➡
I wanted to become a pathologist, so I study diseases rather than patients.
診察はしていなくて
病気の研究をしています｡
趣味は料理と食べることです｡
食事係なら任せて下さい｡
I like to cook and eat.
I can handle our meals if you want.
おおっ！それは助かるわ｡
Oh? That would really help.
I-Itou?
い…伊東さん｡
｢せりか｣って いい名前だね｡
あの～何か…ひびきが｡
I like the name Serika.
It has a nice sound.
えっ!?そ…そうですか｡
R-Really?
(生徒)えっと…僕の名前は➡
Uh, my name is Yuuki, with "yuu" meaning kindness, and "ki" for hope.
優しさと希望に満ちあふれ…
輝く子になる➡
という意味があり
優希にしたそうです｡
超～緊張した｡アッハハ…｡
I was so nervous!
Okay, next up is Itou.
はいはい｡じゃあ 次…伊東さん｡
(先生)伊東さん！
えっ…はい｡
Itou...
Yes.
(先生)伊東さん…？
Itou?
The
Mea
ni
ng
of
My
Na
me
(せりか父)ただいま｡➡
I'm home.
Serika?
どうしたんだ？
せりかのやつ 俺のこと無視して｡
What's wrong with Serika?
She seems to be ignoring me.
あなたが名前に意味が
ないとか言ったからよ｡
Because you told her that her name doesn't mean anything.
他の子は み～んな意味が
込められてるのに➡
All her classmates have names with meanings.
So she was the only one without one.
自分だけないから…｡
あ…｡しまったなこりゃ…｡
I guess I screwed up...
(父)せりか…入るぞ｡
Serika,
I'm coming in.
悪かったよ｡
もう｢せりか｣って呼ぶのやめて！
Sorry.
Don't call me Serika!
嫌いになった！
I hate that name.
意味がない名前って
みんなに笑われた｡
Everyone laughed at me because my name doesn't mean anything...
(父)ごめんな…せりか｡
ちゃんと話せば良かったな…➡
Sorry, Serika.
I should have told you the whole story.
せりかが生まれる前は もっと
いっぱい名前の候補があったんだ｡➡
Before you were born,
we prepared a whole list of names.
いろ～んな意味の…｡
Different names with different meanings.
でも全然 決められなかった｡➡
But we couldn't decide on one.
意味を１つに
しぼれなくてさ…お父さん｡
Your dad couldn't settle on a single meaning.
(父)それで…生まれたての
せりかの顔を見た時➡
Once you were born and I saw your face,
何となく
出てきたんだよ…せりかって｡
I just thought of the name Serika.
There wasn't any meaning behind that name,
(父)名前に意味はなかったけど
それでも良いと思った｡➡
but I still liked it.
｢せりか｣って
呼びたくなったんだ｡
I wanted to call you Serika.
そう呼びたかったから…
｢せりか｣にした｡
I named you Serika
because I wanted to call you that.
現在
Se—
せり…いや 伊東さん｡
Er, I-Itou...
I'll help you with the cooking.
食事係 俺もやるよ｡
料理 好きだし｡
ホントですか？
I like to cook.
Really? Thank you so much.
ありがとうございます！
じゃあ 缶詰も分類するんで➡
Then I'll sort through the canned goods, so could you bring them in?
取ってきてもらえますか？
ほ～い｡
Sure.
あの…南波さん！
Um, Nanba?
Huh?
You can call me by my first name.
私の名前…下の名前で
呼んでくれていいですよ｡
えっ…い…いいんですか？
はい｡
Huh? C-Can I really?
Yes.
自分の名前
気に入ってるんです｡
I happen to like my name.
(先生)伊藤さん｡昨日の➡
Itou, will you be able to tell us the meaning of your name today?
名前の意味
ちゃんと発表できる？
はい！
Yes!
私の名前は 伊東せりかです｡
My name is Itou Serika.
名前に意味は…ありません！
My name
doesn't have a meaning!
The stars I admired were too bright for me
so I quietly closed my eyes
I have faith in you, as you stand alone, full of doubts
I'm right here, next to you
Come now, take my hand and hold it tight
If you do, we will always
have hope, shine with light
and overcome whatever we might face
Do you see how wonderful this world is
and how our future unfolds?
Even the tears we shed and could not put into words
will one day dry up, I am sure
One by one the smiles spread
and ascend towards the starlit sky
＜閉鎖環境での次の課題は➡
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#13 3-D Ant
Our next task in this sealed environment is to write a paper on space exploration's importance.
宇宙開発の大切さをわかって
もらうための文章を作ること＞
＜それを考える中
私が思い出したのは➡
That was when I recalled something Hibito and I heard from Noguchi Soichi when we were kids.
ひびと
子供の頃 日々人と聞いた
のぐち　そういち
宇宙飛行士 野口聡一さんの話だ＞
＜ええ 今日はですね 僕は
何で人間が宇宙に行くか➡
Today, I would like to discuss why humans should go into space.
…ということを
お話ししたいと思います｡➡
僕は そういう時に ひとつの
たとえ話を いつもします＞
There's this metaphor I like to use.
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"3-D Ant".
＜すげえぞ 日々人
本物の野口さんだ＞
Wow, Hibito! It's the real Noguchi!
(日々人)＜うん！野口さんだ！＞
Yep, it's Noguchi!
(日々人)パンパカパ～ン！
This Week's Space Photo
This week's space photo!
今週の宇宙写真です！
スッゲェ！
Awesome!